[Music]
new york city make some noise for the
one and only
[Music]
wow thank you guys so much
please please sit sit sit oh my
goodness
look at this
new york city
are here thank god i've been traveling i
was just in texas and i got my first
taste of southern hospitality on the
plane because there was a baby crying
and some lady yelled out if you don't
shut that baby up and feed it i'll take
my titty out and feed it myself
so then i started crying
i'm a baby
[Applause]
well welcome thank you guys so much for
being here
i've been all around this country
because of this amazing technology known
as tick tock
clap if you're here from tick tock
tick tock has given all of you add
and turned it into money for me
and all i can say is thank you china
i love china
china is the greatest country in the
world
matter of fact i learned some mandarin
for my chinese overlords because xiong
kong shi woman duh which translates to
hong kong belongs to china i love china
[Applause]
speaking of china any asians here
[Music]
okay i like how most of the indians stay
quiet good job guys
that was a test
that's right i'm not going to start
rapping asians now indians and asians
have a beef since calculus class
i'm a on asians okay i got asian
friends with strong asian names like
john and victor the good guys
this whole stop asian hate movement i
don't know how i feel about it
don't get me wrong don't get me wrong i
don't condone the violence i actually
went to a stop agent hate march at least
i thought i did turns out i was just
online at supreme and
struggle is real
but the whole asian hate movement is
emblematic of a much larger problem in
this country see in this country we
never treat the disease we only treat
the symptom see we don't need to stop
asian hate we need to stop american
stupidity that's what needs to happen
stop don't clap
[Applause]
people start beating up asians because
some got on tv and said asians
have a highly contagious virus
someone tells you asians have a highly
contagious disease and your first
instinct is to get within fighting
distance of this person
what's that you got aids let me you
in the ass just to show you what happens
what are we doing
i knew at a very early age not to
with asian people because my best friend
in high school was this chinese kid he
was so chinese he was valedictorian and
he was also a swimmer 100 all muscle
you'd have to have brain damage to
with him so naturally a hockey player
did and
one day i saw him shoulder check this
ice jockey into a concrete wall i was
like bro why the hell did you just do
that like he called me the worst thing
you could call a chinese person japanese
[Laughter]
it's been humbling to travel this
country and realize i have fans
it made me think of who my first fans
were
and it had to be my grandparents
my grandma was the first person to ever
laugh in my face on purpose
i was four years old she's like you look
like mr bean
i thought it was a compliment
[Laughter]
i know you see it it's fine
i've come to terms with it to those of
you that don't find mr being attractive
i assure you mr bean
all day every day you want it you can
get it i got you
mr bean i'm gonna put that on a
t-shirt for sure
just
[Laughter]
my grandparents are the reason i'm funny
i remember the first joke i ever told
was to my grandpa i was five years old
and to avoid an ass whooping i used a
joke he was towering over me he said
something in gujarati
days which translates to i'll put your
head between your ears and i'm down
there like it's already there bro
he started laughing i was like oh
and i ran to my grandmother's arms
should i come in mr bean and
from that point on i knew comedy could
be used to avoid painful situations
i try to laugh at everything
laughing at death
you ever think about death all the time
all the time
what's your name
john
all the time
you know how you want to go
in a raging inferno
what's wrong with you
you ever start a conversation with
someone and be like man i should not
have done that
[Laughter]
like you asked your uber driver i had
the days going and then they responded
like oh my bad bro i didn't
i was just raised well
you know how i want to go
i want to die a burden to my family
that's how
i want to go like 10 years after i'm
supposed to i'ma leave a bunch of
competing wills and some confusing
documents
like a do not resuscitate and then
resuscitate using oral sex only you're
all kind of wild
if you gotta die you might as well be
annoying you know
i've been thinking about death a lot
because i got a city bike and
if you've never questioned your own
mortality
get a city bike
just the other day i was cruising
listening to drake
and
and i almost got t-boned by a volvo
that would have been a hilarious
headline though comedian killed by one
of the safest cars in the world god's
plan
death
been thinking about death a lot
is the only thing we all have in common
we're all going to die
that's my friend kevin barnett's catch
phrase we're all gonna die he was a
jamaican man from florida and whenever
he was bombing he said we all gonna die
he would bomb so hard he had to remind
people the futility of human existence
we're all gonna die and then you guessed
it he died
that's the funniest joke he ever told
this should win a mark twain prize
that's how funny that is because
mark twain also famously predicted his
own death and love using the n-word as
much as jamaican man from florida
don't cough a game
can't be coughing now what the you
doing
what's wrong with you
this whole shit's about to get shut down
it's a very expensive production
in the front row who the
i know why you've been thinking about
death
killing everyone around you
jesus christ
i almost died recently
i almost died last year john
hell i'll tell you
you ever died
you've never died you ever been blackout
drunk
congratulations
you've died
blacking out is when you die john
blacking out is when you die and you
wake up in a new space-time continuum
and you've been afforded a brand new
opportunity to live your life in an
entirely different way and yet 24 hours
later you're like shot shot shot shot
shots
i died last year during the summer of
hard seltzer
truly's high noons and of course white
claw
one night i had 20 mango white claw
that's not exaggeration over five hours
i had 20 mango white claw after seven
they're just water you know
and i got blackout drunk and i hopped on
a city bike in chinatown new york
yeah you know chinatown that place full
of really good drivers and pedestrians
that always look both ways chinatown
blackout drunk in chinatown and i know i
died because i saw my life flash before
my eyes when i saw all the chickens that
ever consumed hanging in a restaurant
window
blackout drunk rode four miles no shirt
no helmet no recollection
get home to my wife and she's heated
it's like what the how the did
you get home you could have died i said
the coldest i've ever said i said
it ain't living if you ain't dying
what's that mean i don't know
i hope to find out someday
passed out on the punishment couch
obviously
woke up the next morning and i had to
re-evaluate my relationship with alcohol
i took a long hard look in the mirror
and said you know what
it's time to quit biking great decision
i never leave you mango
you're my one and only
you ever thought about your relationship
with alcohol
yeah you have
that's what you have by the way you have
a relationship with alcohol anything you
bring to your lips that often you at
least hang it and bang it you understand
americans we have a very abusive
relationship with alcohol we drank more
in the last two years than we've ever
drank in the history of this country you
know that we drank more in the last two
years than we've ever drank in the
history of this country americans looked
death in the face and said cheers
and i know this firsthand because my dad
has a liquor store
cash only obviously and
i would talk to my dad every day dad
stop going to work you're not essential
i don't want you get hurt i don't you
get sick you're a smoker stop going to
work you're like no knee mesh these
people need to drink
and i didn't get it i don't understand
why i understand why we were drinking so
much until my wife and i both got
coronavirus we were locked up in the
house for two weeks at the end of those
two weeks i called my dad said dad
you're preventing murder suicide every
day thank you so much
thank you so much for your service every
day at seven o'clock i clap for my dad
i'm like yeah you the real hero man
these doctors
i've been thinking about my relationship
to alcohol i owe most of my life to
alcohol my love of hip hop for one is
from alcohol because my dad's store was
in a black neighborhood he'd come home
with the wildest cds the first album i
ever listened to was hip hop's hardest
hits it was dead wrong by biggie hit him
up by tupac and the rough riders anthem
by dmx and yo i heard ant
i was like yo i need timberland boots
immediately
my eighth grade picture is me in tan
tim's a silver roughriders chain and
green contacts
i had no idea who i was but when that
chain oxidized it really brought out my
eyes it's beautiful
indians have a very interesting
relationship with alcohol and i don't
mean native americans i mean my people
any natives here
wow
what have we done
i've only met one native american my
whole life
it was in the whitest place that ever
been denver colorado and he had the most
indian name i ever heard larry
bearshield
and i was out after a show and i see
another brown person i was like hey man
uh just checking in just in case some
goes down i got your back you got
mine you know me
and i was like are you latino or
something he goes nah man i'm first
nation
i was like is that some kind of mexican
gang or
no i'm native american i was like oh
yeah indian me too let's have a drink he
did not like that
cut to two hours later me and larry are
up
and larry is hilarious i was like larry
what are you doing here in denver and he
leaned in real close he's like man i'm
i'm visiting my friends they're part of
bill cosby's favorite tribe arapaho oh
my god
larry
now me and larry are best friends okay
larry and i start playing this drinking
game called take shots and be racist i
don't know if you've ever played it
before but if you're not being racist
while drunk with your friends you're
wasting both friendship and alcohol
and larry starts going off the rails
almost immediately he's like us indians
we got a lot in common right like you
love all that corny ass jewelry you guys
can't handle your liquor us natives
we're real spiritual but you guys you
guys worship monkeys i was like larry
that's some hacky ass racism you better
watch your mouth before i build a
pipeline through it
we're friends
and now larry's time of hot chopping me
i'm yoga flaming him we're having a
great god damn time
at one point we're getting so loud the
bartender pours two drinks and he tries
to cut us off takes him back and larry
turns him he's like listen man you can't
indian give to some indians
i'm like yeah larry you tell that
cracker
now larry and i are trashed okay
and i finally asked him larry
why does this stereotype exist that
native americans drink so much and he
gets up all angry and he's like we
drink a lot because the colonizer robbed
us and raped us and left us with this
fire water to deal with our generational
trauma he's all humping around and
jumping around like larry relax
it's gonna start raining
[Laughter]
and he gives me a big old bear hug he's
a you piece of
and he sits down
and
and he reaches into his satchel
and he pulls out this turquoise
medallion this beautiful turquoise
medallion and he hands it to me as a
prize for being the best racist
he says he says nemesh i want you to
have this may bring you good fortune and
protect you from evil spirits like
tequila
i couldn't help resist saying thank you
larry i'll wear it to the casino and
and then i run to the bathroom take a
piss and pack a piece pipe and when i
come back larry is gone like a wolf in
the night
and then i get the check
and i realize larry has manifest
destined me out of 300 this piece of
that's reparations i'll take it it's
fine
[Music]
well i wish he stayed though i wish
larry stayed at the bar because then i
would have told him that indians like me
also drink because we also got robbed
specifically at liquor stores at
gunpoint
that's what my dad drinks
my dad would drink because he's been
robbed he's been shot at for like 400
bucks that's why i drink because kids
emulate behavior when i was 13 i saw my
dad come home after having a tough day
go to the garage with his white friend
johnny walker black and
put himself a little whiskey like can't
believe it i almost died i drowned that
demon you know i was 13
i had a tough day
i'd done poorly on a math test
went to the garage point myself a little
johnny walker black
can't believe it
i got a 97
[Laughter]
now what do you think happens after we
die
blackness nothing
yeah
new jersey
[Laughter]
where is my accent from
this is what i think this is what i
think happens when you die okay i think
your body dissolves but your souls are
born into different vessels go through
this iterative process perfecting your
souls until you reach perfection and
then you're released into the universe
from whence we came that's what i think
happens
[Music]
i stopped drinking as much but i started
doing a lot more lsd and let me tell you
it's been fantastic
i highly recommend it it's a great drug
that is a hindu belief any religious
people here by the way
none
okay
everyone else just a bunch of little
nazixes huh
everyone's just twerking on satan
are you all rich
yeah you never meet poor atheists
oh no we don't need god we got cash bro
who do you blame for your problems
yourselves
no wonder y'all been drinking so much
some of my favorite people religious
kobe bryant
religious
he was at church the morning he died
granted he had a lot to repent for but
he was trying
oh you're not laughing
soft
you guys are softer than joe biden's
diapers soft
soft as
i subscribe to kobe bryant's mama
mentality the mamba mentality if you're
unaware says perfect yourself every day
get better every day until you reach
perfection that's the central tenet of
hinduism y'all say mamba i say gita huh
wow
a bunch of kwame browns in this
[Laughter]
i'm hindu but not like narendra modi
hates muslims hindu but i do think i'm
better than christians
oh now you're religious all of a sudden
listen if you're offended by anything
i've said just trust that all these
words were written by god okay
i'm really an instrument
i've been on christianity all
across this country and christians have
been really upset
i'm christian i was like i bet you won't
make fun of islam why don't you make fun
of islam because i don't want to get
charlie hebdo okay that's a fair reason
i was sitting on christianity in
indianapolis to the point where this
priest was in the crowd got up and left
this guy whose sole job it is to listen
to confession people say the worst
ever got up and said every knee shall
bow and by some divine inspiration i
said yeah to suck jesus jesus's gay ass
dick
[Laughter]
i'm going to hell
psych that place ain't real
i almost converted to christianity
because of christmas
christmas almost got me but then my
parents they hatched a plan
when i was like nine years old i wanted
to autograph michael jordan basketball
for christmas and they got me an
autographed anthony hardaway basketball
to ask for a michael jordan autographed
basketball and get an anthony hardaway
autographed basketball it's like asking
for an iphone and getting an anthony
hardaway autographed basketball
i was so upset but i was opening the box
up right i was like oh yes it's a
basketball shaped box like oh here it is
and i opened this up like every
hard way i hate jesus my parents
like yes jesus is the devil
hinduism has its flaws
the caste system
the worst set of rules that exist across
any religious
system the caste system if you're
unaware is a system that dictates what
jobs people can basically have allowing
people's money and status in society it
was the inspiration for the amazon
corporate ladder if you're unaware
it's pronounced cost but that's how they
say it in england and that country
entirely so i'll just keep saying pass
yeah that's right any british people
here
shut the up
england as a record label or staff
and as a crew
[Music]
when prince philip died i jerked off
i did i masturbated to the idea of
coming in his mouth like hey how's that
for assault taxi colonial
i'm sorry
hinduism is great
it's great it's a great religion if
you're in the market
great food great parties
no molestation
unless you join bikram yoga in which
case at this point is your fault okay
there's no conversion process either you
just got to go to union square put on an
orange loincloth and say hoodie krishna
a few times
america is already a fairly hindu place
as i think about it
the main stereotype i got growing up
kids would be like
you guys worship cows right you guys
worship cows that's what american kids
will say
i can't think of a group of people that
worship cows more than americans
you just worship cows the same way you
worship jesus you eat the
okay
yeah i know all about communion you're
not gonna get away from it you you eat
flesh you drink blood you almost drown a
baby you're against abortion okay
christians whatever you say
there's this group of hindus there's
this group of hindus in new jersey that
built a 10 million temple but instead of
using labor from the united states they
imported
lower caste labor kept them on temple
grounds paid them nothing and said god
want you to do it this way
that's the most american i ever
heard no
i was introduced to hinduism when i was
five
my mom put a giant red dot on my
forehead i was like go to school it'll
protect you from evil
it did not
i'll just go to school and every kid
named john paul and peter are like you
got a little red dot on your head pew
pew
i'm like shut the up you ash
wednesday
anger's one of these vices supposed to
get rid of as a hindu but we also
believe in reincarnation so that's the
next guy's problem i don't give a
and to conclude my point i can't think
of anything more american than putting a
target on a kid's head and send them to
school no that's pretty american
soft
ass crap
[Applause]
this is the last thing i'll say about
hinduism it helped get me laid
long before the kama sutra i was going
to this thing called gerba
the new jersey indians have identified
themselves
gurba is this religious festival that
would happen september and october to
celebrate the hindu holiday of navratri
indians and hindus would gather in a
high school to dance around a statue of
god for three to four hours to celebrate
the triumph of good over evil
it'd also be where teenagers would go to
celebrate the triumph of hormones over
everything
we just dance and be all sweaty and talk
to each other with samosa breath and
then
and then if it didn't work out we end up
at a taco bell drive through yelling hey
substitute beans in that pizza bro
i grew up in a town called parsippany
new jersey
[Music]
parsippany is a town named after larry
bearshield type indians and now run by
h1b ass indians
h1bs if you're unaware are the people
that actually stole the jobs and let
mexicans take all the blame
i got a bunch of h1b cousins like yeah
keep blaming the mexicans we'll be right
here
earning this good white money
i got h1b fans i can sense some of you
are here right now
most of you are great but some of these
h1bs have lost their minds because i
talk a lot of about narendra modi
on the internet and all these h1b is
like how dare you say something about to
run the morty you know anything about
india
i'm like relax mom
narendra modi lifted india out of
poverty don't you say anything about
narendra modi a word
you open up more call centers so you
could scan white people out of money go
that's dope
i got a call from a scammer the other
day this india dude call me hi can i
talk to nimish patel this is jeff
[Applause]
no it ain't bro
no one named jeff has ever pronounced
nemesh patel correctly okay
i got a plan you do the back end work
i'll do the voice we'll clean up in this
now what's your social
security number
parsippany was so indian that my
elementary school had a translator
another eight-year-old indian kid that
would translate
that would translate for any indian kid
that couldn't speak english and i
transferred from one side of parsimony
to the other side of parsippany in first
grade right around christmas time and i
was so upset i decided i would pretend
to not speak any english
i'm sitting there crying at my desk and
they send this little eight-year-old kid
over and say hey buddy i'll translate
for you man no need to cry i got you bro
i was like shut the up
i speak english i'm just trying to ride
this out to a break
if you snitch i swear to god i'll put
your head between your ears you
understand me
so then he started crying
that night i went home
and my sister and i stayed up super late
watching home alone setting traps for my
dad
that the next morning i had forgotten my
ruse that i didn't speak any english
and the teacher is reading something
she's like sally holds a apple i was
like i believe it's an apple
she goes you speak english
it's a christmas miracle
thank you white santa
parsippany by the time i was in high
school
had so many indians that i was patel
number eight
my senior class had 22 patels and i
would always get this question why are
so many patels and why there's so many
patels because we killed all the smiths
that's why
it's over for you
and when you grow up surrounded by that
many of your own people you learn this
value called resilience because you know
people always have your back
you could not be racist towards indian
kids and parsippany i remember one time
some kid was like you guys did 9 11. i
was like yeah we did 9 11. we'll do it
again too
i got 19 cousins right here i'm sure one
of us knows how to fly it's all
trigonometry bro we'll figure that
out you wanna go let's go
my sister's one of the most resilient
people i know
because she went through this oh indian
names are so weird indian names are so
exotic they're so weird what does your
name mean
her name is noka
it means boat
not like hand carved canoe or or
beautiful sailing vessel just regular
ass boat
and she could have gotten her whole life
pissed off annoyed at her name but
instead she flipped it this year for
halloween she went lil yachty you
understand resilience
ss resilience
i grew up so indian we go to indian only
parties
every friday and saturday night every
indian teenager in the trice area after
gerber would descend upon club platinum
in new brunswick new jersey
club platinum if you don't know was the
epicenter of some of the greatest indian
parties of all time but yo you've never
seen so many honda accords and toyota
camrys
me and my five cousins would roll six
deep in a toyota camry wearing different
color express shirts
looking like cell phone kiosk operators
depth gel out the ass stiff as
and we go to platinum and we sniff girls
hair that's what we did that was our
move
we called ourselves the cuomo's you know
and we were pregame in the parking lot
of a dunkin donuts
if you don't understand every dunkin
donuts in the northeast is owned and
operated by indian people we basically
be pre-gaming like our cousin's driveway
and our pre-game would be one bottle of
bacardi
one bottle of coca-cola and one bottle
of curved cologne
curve if you don't know is a cologne
when you put it on women go around you
one night we got so up that we
had to sleep in the car the next morning
there's six indians in neon shirts
hung over in a toyota camry in the
parking lot of a dunkin donuts
and then there's a knock on the window
and it's an indian cop
and i look up and my first thought is an
indian cop
his parents must be mad disappointed
i'll roll down the window and say
what are you boys doing here
luckily i was quick enough to just be
like
waiting to start our shift officer
you want a french vanilla i got you
i started drinking my senior year i had
my first step with alcohol when i was 13
and thank god that johnny walker black
is disgusting to a 13 year old indian
kid because if it was something
delicious like mango white club
i definitely would have drank all
throughout high school i would end up at
rutgers university
[Applause]
and then i'd definitely be a doctor
right that's of course
that's the path
thank you johnny walker black for saving
my life
don't get me wrong i was still pre-med
obviously
i was pre-med finance at nyu
i could have been most of you people
but i dropped pre-med in my junior year
because i got a c in organic chemistry i
got a c in organic chemistry because i
failed the lab i failed the lab because
we were making some compound in this lab
and i accidentally made some cocaine
adjacent compound
and then i inhaled this compound to the
point where my heart started beating out
of my chest and the lab tech was like
you failed the lab and uh if this keeps
up you got to go to the hospital
and that night i went home and i
realized i didn't want to be a doctor
and since i couldn't do cocaine i
couldn't do finance either right
now here i am
what a time
thank god i get to spread laughter
because apparently this country no
longer believes that medicine is the
best medicine
[Laughter]
we'll try anything else but medicine no
no no no
science is for retards what
what there's people that don't believe
in science in this country and they're
not even black
black people have a legit historical
gripe against science the rest of us are
eating ketchup ignoring the fact that
ketchup is science
you realize that ketchup is science it's
tomatoes and high fructose corn syrup
that's science
i only bring that up because i think
there's a strong correlation between
people that don't believe in science and
also consume a lot of ketchup you know
what i mean you know what i'm saying you
know it's okay
[Applause]
but i don't disagree
i don't trust medicine either
because healthcare is a criminal
enterprise
health care is a criminal enterprise
it is
i wasn't concerned about getting
covered
and dying when it's your time to go you
go
i was concerned about getting covert
being in a hospital for two weeks and
then coming out with the bill for two
million dollars that's what i was
terrified of
that happened to multiple people in this
country the greatest country in the
world multiple people got two million
dollar bills for having coronavirus
if i was in a coma for two weeks and i
came out with a bill for two million
dollars i would laugh myself back into
the coma
two million dollars yeah put the on
china's tab i paid for that
call up xi jinping tom nemesis hotel
owes them 2 million 2 million
2 million dollars
because healthcare is a criminal
enterprise
healthcare has this virus known as
capitalism
that i really just heard is all my
finance friends being like another
communist here we go
god damn right i'm communist i love
china do you understand
and this virus has obviously infected
hospital companies billing companies
pharmaceutical companies they're
but now this virus has gone on to
doctors
and i know this firsthand because i have
16 first
cousins five of them are doctors and all
we do is argue about health care prices
in america why don't you do something
about health care prices and all my
doctor cousins say the same thing our
hands are tied okay our hands are tied
it's a system that's broken
which is the dorkiest way of saying
don't hate the player hit the game
doctors don't do because their
hands are tied with money that's what
the problem is
listen we care about people we don't do
it for the money and then they drive off
into tesla it's like wait what bro what
mother teresa never had no model 3.
they don't do anything they won't even
change the price of band-aids you know
how much a 15-cent band-aid is in a new
york city hospital a 15-cent band-aid
seven dollars
because apparently the hospital is also
the mini bar at the ritz carlton seven
dollars
seven seven dollars there's never some
fly band-aid doesn't have elmo on it
it's not an off-white band-aid that says
band-aid just a regular
regular band-aid
you know what your need cost in this
country
25 000
you know what your toyota camry costs
22 000.
and i've never known a need to get 192
000 miles
you can't get a discount on a knee
you can't hobble it's a doctor's office
hey say bro anything you do come on man
come on man come on please please come
on man
the doctor would be like well you could
suck my dick but
the irony would be too profound you
getting on two knees to get one new one
get the out of my office
[Applause]
see the problem is that we treat doctors
like saints in this country but really
to me they're like prostitutes
they provide a necessary service you can
identify them by their clothing and if
you can't pay they have you buy the
balls
but at least prostitutes have the
decency to tell you how much they're
going to charge
with a doctor you just get
go ask any doctor hey hey doc how much
is this procedure about to provide
i don't know you got to talk to my pimp
blue cross blue shield i got nothing to
do with that man
and doctors get real upset when i talk
all this oh you're just jealous you
weren't smart enough to become a
physician
listen anyone can go to the caribbean
okay it's not that difficult
it ain't easy but it ain't hard
doctors all justify their high salaries
by saying
we get paid so much because med school
is so expensive okay and i understand
that okay
hear me out here's the solution i
proposed how about
we eliminate all medical school debt
we eliminate
all medical school debt and then we pay
doctors minimum wage
don't worry there'll be tips cash tips
thanks for keeping the lube warm doc
any doctors here
collab if you're a doctor you're a
doctor where the other doctors at
doctors doctors
okay staff please make note of where the
doctors at
and by the way if you're afraid of
saying you're a doctor just pretend i'm
a pharmaceutical sales rep
okay we got we got doctors here got
doctor here doctor here i know i've been
harsh as a special treat on your way out
you'll be charged 400 for no
reason
surprise medical bill
that's what happens facility fee for
stepping into this
i don't fully blame doctors
obviously insurance companies and all
that they deserve most of the blame
doctors are our last line of defense but
i also think
americans do not deserve health care
we need it
deserve is the wrong word
we don't care about our health how do
you deserve health care if you don't
care about your health i know i don't
deserve health care
i recently discovered exactly how much
weed someone needs to smoke to have an
asthma attack
and i had an asthma attack
i went to a travis god concert
back when it was still okay to do okay
you with travis scott john hell
yeah
travis scott is one of my favorite
artists i was listening to him on the
way here and i heard a lyric that was so
funny i almost fell off my city bike
i was eating that punan got my bangs wet
we gonna have to change for the banquet
dripping
you understand the lyric
he's so deep in the he's car
washing with his bangs you see
and now the juice has gotten on
the alpha he was gonna wear to this
banquet he was attending but it's been
ruined
what a poet
[Applause]
i went to a travis scott concert and i
smoked four blunts in an hour
and then
that song stopped trying to be god came
on i was like you're right travis i have
to go to the hospital
and i called an uber to the hospital
because they don't let ambulances in at
travis scott concerts
[Applause]
now called an uber to the hospital
because an ambulance is six hundred
dollars and i'm not going to die a
sucker right
now get to the hospital nyu langone in
cobble hill brooklyn and now i have
asthma so i know exactly what i need
doctor i'm having an asthma attack
you're having an asthma attack i need
albuterol nebulizer you need albuterol
nebulizer
is this self-checkout what's going on
bro
give me my medicine
he's like you'll be fine and he scuttles
away in his ferragamo loafers
and he sends in a nurse where's the menu
of all the other i could be getting
since i've stopped in at casa de nyu
blood work ekg
x-ray
now they're not
trying to treat me for a heart attack
what they're doing is running up the
insurance tab because insurance will
just pay whatever hospital says luckily
i said the magic words i said i don't
have coverage
she threw an inhaler at me
she was like get out you wheezy broke
i'm in and out in an hour and a half
get home
two weeks later get the bill
six thousand dollars
i had another asthma attack
[Music]
six six thousand six thousand dollars
for an hour and a half and i didn't come
once
luckily i was raised by indian people
who tell me that the price is never the
price until you talk about the price
that's where we're at in america
you gotta haggle for your life these
days i called the hospital i said listen
i'm not gonna give you six thousand
dollars they say why not i said well for
one you already gave me the medicine
two i don't have six thousand dollars
now i have six thousand dollars but i
also know a little bit about the health
care system i know that you get sick at
the beginning of the year like i did
every hospital has this giant pool of
money they have to give away for free
care in order to stay non-profit
sidebar if you get corona in december
just hold on okay
hold on
but know this i know this as i'm talking
this lady look i don't have six thousand
dollars i'm not gonna give you six
thousand i don't have six thousand
dollars they literally said how much do
you have
did i call the mob who the
i got nothing you break my knees if you
want i'm not giving you six thousand
dollars
all right miss patel no need to get
irate
listen you don't owe us anything but
please understand that if you truly
can't pay you don't always anything but
if you can pay and you're not paying you
might be taking six thousand dollars out
of pocket for someone who truly can't
pay i was like
don't hate the player hit the game click
i was so glad i finessed nyu out of six
thousand dollars but then i remembered i
went to nyu and they're so up about two
hundred thousand dollars
life's about small victories
after almost dying you kind of
reevaluate your life you know i've been
trying to be a better person
trying to work out a lot more
only because i think i'm going to fight
kamel nanjiani at some point
i've trained him for that day
kumail if you don't know is a fantastic
comedian he's pakistani and he's jacked
if every pakistani was as big as kumail
is they would have never caught bin
laden
i'm pitching a movie to kumail right now
we want to remake the movie nastic
it's about 1947 india when partition
happened when the brits left india they
divided the subcontinent into bangladesh
pakistan and india and they divided it
up against really crooked borders i'm
guessing using the outlines of their
teeth and
and when they left
this this partition caused the exodus of
millions of people and the death of like
two million people in the movie the
pakistanis and the indians hate each
other but in my version with kumail we
team up and rewrite history in glorious
bastard style
we go to england right and then we
seduce winston churchill's wife
and then we find winston churchill
grab him by his fat ass cheeks and say
for the first time in history that's why
we your you fat
i'm trying to be a better
person i am i really am i am trying to
be a better person
i'm trying to identify moments when i'm
mad and turn them into moments of
laughter this came to a full head a
little while ago when there was a
hurricane in new york hurricane ida hit
new york and i had to go do a show
and i called an suv to come pick me up
as i'm stepping into this suv i missed
the curb so instead of stepping into
this suv i step into six inches of new
york city rain water
so now i got aids foot right
it's a clinical term
now
i get into this suv and i'm pissed off
right i can't go back upstairs i'm
already late so i take my boot off i
pour all this water out take my sock off
slam it on the seat take this dude's
hand sanitizer squeeze it into my hands
rub it all between my toes and now my
hands sticky my foot is sticky i'm
pissed off i take this sock i wring it
dry and i hang it in the suv's ac vent
you know
and i'm checking if the driver is
looking at now i'm pissed off
and hanging and trying to drive this
sock and i catch myself in the rear view
mirror i'm like oh
i am mr bean just
[Applause]
i never laughed harder in my life
i'm trying to be the person i am on
molly at all times you know what i mean
generous sexually fluid all those things
you ever done mine before
how old are you
28 yeah you don't deserve it yet
all these teens and 20 year olds doing
drugs they don't deserve them i just
started doing drugs in my 30s
in my teens and 20s i was trying to
figure out who i am as a person who i am
as a man in my 30s i realized i ain't
i'm gonna do all the drugs they are
you got to go through that journey
before you start doing drugs
you never done mine before
the way it works is it releases all the
serotonin in your brain for three to
four hours so you're the happiest you've
ever been and then for the next two to
four days you want to commit suicide
but for those three to four hours
you feel like a 21 year old white woman
it's incredible
the scientific term is mdma it stands
for
damn molly's amazing it's incredible
the reason i love molly so much is
that's a very communal drug
it brings people together it's all love
when you're on mali if we're dropping
miley instead of bombs there'll be no
problems in the world
the last time i did mali went to this
warehouse party in brooklyn that's where
they have them they used to kill people
there now 30 year olds go find
themselves
and at this warehouse party they're
playing edm music electronic dance music
but on top of it that overlaid martin
luther king jr's i have a dream speech
it sounds ridiculous but it's the freest
i've ever felt
now i'm i'm peeking on molly as martin
luther king jr is dropping some of the
hottest lines in human history
and i look around and i see black men
and white men
jews and
gentiles protestants and catholics all
holding hands and singing the words that
negro spiritual levels by avicii
free at last free at last thank god on
molly free at last
that joke is for people who know martin
luther king jr and also levels by avicii
so it's a weird venn diagram
i considered stopping doing mali
because i was talking to this
neurologist and he was telling me that
once all the serotonin in your brain is
depleted your receptor's taken dopamine
and that dopamine breaks down into
peroxide destroying your serotonin
receptors effectively ending your
ability to experience happiness in the
near future but as he's telling me this
i kind of zoned out
and when i came back into the
conversation he was talking about how
all lives matter i was like oh i can't
trust this dude at all man i'ma just
keep dancing
but i wean myself off of molly because
now i do shrooms
shrooms are so much better they're all
natural they're very cathartic
the first time i did shrooms i cried for
30 minutes i was like well me and my dad
ever be best friends
the second time i did shrooms i cried
for 30 minutes that was a piece of
to my mom
now the third time i did shrooms like
i got to dose my parents
right gonna tell my mom it's are you
vedic medicine here you go
my parents are here by the way give it
up for them they're in the back
gonna be a very difficult conversation
later
because they knew about the drug use but
they did not know about the asthma
attack
i'm alive
my parents are my biggest fans they
watch everything i do
my dad saw me smoking weed on a youtube
live stream
and
my dad called me almost immediately
nemesh what are you smoking
i said it's weird dad
said you need to quit
i said okay i'll quit smoking weed if
you quit smoking cigarettes
he said the most dead ever
i'm not gonna argue with you
yeah dad we just had the argument you
lost it's fine take the l
bro he said i'll get you back they hung
up and a few moments later i started
seeing all the dislikes on my youtube
videos go up by one
it's like dad what are you doing you
with the algorithm bro
stop then 10 minutes later i got a call
from my mom nemesh what are you smoking
and she's mad religious i was like hindu
kush
i said don't be smart is that weed you
need to stop it's illegal
i said illegal
so was not paying taxes on that all-cash
liquor store we got going over
i won't tell if you don't
[Applause]
without missing a beat she says nimash
the store's in your name you don't pay
taxes
[Applause]
on myself
she says nemesh need to stop you have
asthma i said mom weed is actually a
bronco dilator
she goes oh now you want to be a doctor
oh that's
cute nemesh point blank i don't want you
to die
i said mom
it ain't living if you ain't dying bro
thank you guys so much that's my time
thank you
[Applause]
one more time
[Music]
so
you